YULIIA DOBROVA

FULL-STACK SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

Email: yuliia.dobrova@gmail.com

Portfolio Website: https://yuliiadobrova.com

Phone: +1(778)-325-3487

https://github.com/YuliaDobrova

Address: Vancouver, BC, Canada

https://www.linkedin.com/in/yuliia-dobrova/

SUMMARY

Experienced Full-Stack Software Developer with a history of over 5 years in application and website development. Skilled in HTML, CSS, SCSS, JavaScript, TypeScript, React, Redux, Node.js, Git.

Worked on various projects, from developing solo-projects and web applications to contributing to social media platforms and school management systems.

Technical background in Civil Design Engineering holding a Bachelor's degree, offering over 10 years of both executive and management positions.

Currently I am looking for a full-time position as a Full-Stack Software Developer, willing to strengthen the team with my skills and desire to create, fix, innovate.

HARD SKILLS

SOFT SKILLS

• Team leadership • Public Speaking

- HTML5
- React
- Rest API
- Bootstrap
- Responsibility
- Problem Solving

- CSS3 JavaScript
- Github
- Redux Toolkit MongoDB Node.js
- jQuery Material-Ul
- Curiosity
- Collaborative Development

- TypeScript
- Deployment
 Express.js
 JSON

- Flexibility
- Agile Methodologies

WORK EXPERIENCE

Research and production enterprise "Ukrradioprom" LLC · Freelance Full-stack Software Developer

April 2023 - January 2024

 Developed a user-friendly web application to efficiently handle clients product database. That resulted in a significant 20% increase in online sales within a period of 6 months.

"Web Tech Company "TensionX" ("SaaS Insiders") · Full-time Front-end Developer

February 2022 - March 2023

- Contributed to collaborative Git practices while working with a team of up to 7 developers, successfully delivering to the customer a **Social Media Platform** meeting deadline in 3 months.
- Developed and improved user functionality in an existing School Management System application.

Dental Center of Dr. Krolyk · Freelance Front-end Developer

November 2021 - January 2022

· Created a website design from scratch and developed it for my client in 2 months (implemented interactivity, real reviews, geolocation, multilingualism, adapted to different devices, deployed to hosting).

Engineering Company "Avtomagistral" LCC · Full-time

September 2018 - February 2021

Civil Design Engineer / Head of the Project Department / Front-end Developer

- Holding the title of Civil Design Engineer with the certificate (license), created drawings in AutoCAD, was engaged in project approvals, supervised the author's projects during construction.
- Managed a team of 30 diverse engineers: geodetic engineers, design engineers, accountant engineers.
- · Completed of 50 infrastructure building projects for new design or reconstruction (roads, bridges, park areas, networks) within a 6 month period meeting deadline.
- Created a multi-page business card website for our company from scratch.

EDUCATION

Backend Basics Bootcamp

March 2024

OneCodeCamp Academy

Full-stack Developer Course

September 2020 - October 2021

GoIT Global - International ed-tech company

Bachelor's Degree in Water Resources Engineering

September 2005 - June 2009

The Faculty of Geography of National University of Kyiv

LANGUAGES

• English (Fluent)

Français (Intermediate)

Ukrainian (Fluent)

Russian (Fluent)